<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_short_description">Learn how to make simple apps in Android Studio!</string>
    <string name="notification_update_title">A new update available!</string>
    <string name="summary_notification_update">A new version of the app is available. Click to update!</string>
    <string name="notification_last_time_used_title">It\'s been a while!</string>
    <string name="summary_notification_last_time_used"> Let\'s free up some space! We are happy you are back!</string>

    <string name="welcome">Welcome</string>
    <string name="summary_browse_terms_of_service_and_privacy_policy">Read and agree to our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy to continue</string>
    <string name="agree">Agree</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="get_the_app_to_watch">Get the app and see the full lesson: %1$s</string>
    <string name="activity_not_found">Activity not found.</string>
    <string name="security_error">A security error occurred. Please try again later.</string>
    <string name="io_error">An input/output error occurred. Please check your network connection or storage and try again.</string>
    <string name="illegal_argument_error">Invalid input or argument provided. Please check the information and try again.</string>
    <string name="unknown_error">An unknown error occurred.</string>

    <string name="studio_bot">Studio Bot</string>

    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="app_info">App info</string>

    <string name="favorites">Favorites</string>

    <string name="settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="display">Display</string>
    <string name="summary_preference_settings_display">Personalize your app\'s look and feel</string>

    <string name="appearance">Appearance</string>
    <string name="dark_theme">Dark theme</string>
    <string name="will_turn_on_automatically_by_system">Will turn on automatically by the system</string>
    <string name="will_never_turn_on_automatically">Will never turn on automatically</string>
    <string name="amoled_mode">AMOLED mode</string>
    <string name="follow_system">Follow System Mode</string>
    <string name="light_mode">Light Mode</string>
    <string name="dark_mode">Dark Mode</string>
    <string name="summary_dark_theme">Dark theme uses a deep background to help keep your battery alive longer</string>

    <string name="dynamic_colors">Dynamic colors</string>
    <string name="summary_preference_settings_dynamic_colors">Apply colors from wallpapers to the app theme</string>

    <string name="app_behavior">App behavior</string>
    <string name="bounce_buttons">Bounce click</string>
    <string name="summary_preference_settings_bounce_buttons">Applies a subtle bounce animation to all clickable elements when clicked</string>

    <string name="navigation">Navigation</string>
    <string name="startup_page">Startup page</string>
    <string name="summary_preference_settings_startup_page">Choose the screen to be displayed when the app starts.</string>
    <string name="dialog_startup_subtitle">Choose your preferred startup page:</string>
    <string name="dialog_info_startup">Configures the initial screen presented to users upon launching the application. This setting influences the user\'s first interaction with the app and can be tailored to specific user segments or product goals.</string>

    <string name="language">Language</string>
    <string name="summary_preference_settings_language">Changes the language used in the app</string>
    <string name="dialog_language_subtitle">Select your preferred language</string>
    <string name="dialog_info_language">Personalize your experience with your preferred language. Any language changes you make take effect right away, ensuring a seamless experience in your chosen language</string>

    <string name="notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="summary_preference_settings_notifications">Manage app notifications</string>

    <string name="app_usage_notifications">App Usage Notifications</string>
    <string name="update_notifications">Update Notifications</string>

    <string name="advanced">Advanced</string>
    <string name="summary_preference_settings_advanced">Explore more advanced settings</string>
    <string name="error_reporting">Error reporting</string>
    <string name="bug_report">Bug report</string>
    <string name="summary_preference_settings_bug_report">Send bug reports and feature requests to the app\'s GitHub repository issues page</string>

    <string name="security_and_privacy">Security &amp; privacy</string>
    <string name="summary_preference_settings_privacy_and_security">Manage your privacy settings</string>
    <string name="privacy">Privacy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="summary_preference_settings_privacy_policy">View the policy that governs how we handle your data</string>
    <string name="terms_of_service">Terms of Service</string>
    <string name="summary_preference_settings_terms_of_service">Review the terms you agree to when using our service</string>
    <string name="code_of_conduct">Code of Conduct</string>
    <string name="summary_preference_settings_code_of_conduct">Understand the rules and guidelines for behavior within our service</string>

    <string name="permissions">Permissions</string>
    <string name="summary_preference_settings_permissions">Manage the permissions granted to our service</string>
    <string name="normal">Normal</string>
    <string name="ad_id">Ad id [AD_ID]</string>
    <string name="summary_preference_permissions_ad_id">Allows the app to retrieve and use the advertising identifier associated with the user\'s device, providing personalized ads, measuring ad effectiveness, and showing ads on Android 13 or later devices.</string>
    <string name="internet">Internet [INTERNET]</string>
    <string name="summary_preference_permissions_internet">Allows the app to establish an internet connection to send error reports or check for updates.</string>
    <string name="post_notifications">Post notifications [POST_NOTIFICATIONS]</string>
    <string name="summary_preference_permissions_post_notifications">Allows the app to display notifications on the devices with Android 13 or later.</string>
    <string name="runtime">Runtime</string>
    <string name="access_network_state">Access network state [ACCESS_NETWORK_STATE]</string>
    <string name="summary_preference_permissions_access_network_state">Allows the app to check network connectivity and retrieve information about Wi-Fi, including enabled status and connected Wi-Fi device names.</string>
    <string name="access_notification_policy">Access notification policy [ACCESS_NOTIFICATION_POLICY]</string>
    <string name="summary_preference_permissions_access_notification_policy">Allows the app to access and modify the device\'s notification policy, controlling how and when notifications are displayed to the user and providing custom notification management features.</string>
    <string name="billing">Billing [BILLING]</string>
    <string name="summary_preference_permissions_billing">Allows the app to use the Google Play Billing Library to handle in-app purchases and donations</string>
    <string name="check_license">Check license [CHECK_LICENSE]</string>
    <string name="summary_preference_permissions_check_license">Allows the app to verify its compliance with the license agreement and enforce licensing terms to protect intellectual property.</string>
    <string name="foreground_service">Foreground service [FOREGROUND_SERVICE]</string>
    <string name="summary_preference_permissions_foreground_service">Allows the app to create and use services that run in the foreground, giving them priority over other background processes and improving performance and reliability.</string>

    <string name="ads">Ads</string>
    <string name="summary_preference_settings_ads">Control how we use your information to show you relevant ads</string>
    <string name="display_ads">Display ads</string>
    <string name="personalized_ads">Personalized ads</string>
    <string name="summary_ads_personalized_ads">Choose how we personalize ads for you based on your interests</string>
    <string name="summary_ads">See ads that are relevant to you. Manage the information used to show personalized ads based on your app activity. You can always turn off personalization here.\n</string>

    <string name="usage_and_diagnostics">Usage and diagnostics</string>
    <string name="summary_preference_settings_usage_and_diagnostics">Share data to help improve Cleaner for Android</string>
    <string name="summary_usage_and_diagnostics">Help improve your experience by automatically sending diagnostic, device, and app usage data to us. This will help improve app performance, stability, and other enhancements. Some aggregate data will also help our apps.\n\nThis is general information about your device and how you use our apps (such as battery level, system and app activity, and errors). The data will be used to improve our apps\n\nTurning off this feature doesn\'t affect your device\'s ability to send the information needed for essential services such as app updates and security.\n</string>

    <string name="legal">Legal</string>
    <string name="legal_notices">Legal notices</string>
    <string name="summary_preference_settings_legal_notices">View legal information about our service</string>
    <string name="license">License</string>

    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="summary_preference_settings_about">Learn more about Android Studio Tutorials</string>

    <string name="app_build_version">Application build version</string>
    <string name="summary_preference_settings_oss">License details for open source software</string>
    <string name="device_info">Device Info</string>
    <string name="app_build">App Build: %6$s\n%1$s\n%2$s\n%3$s\n%4$s\n%5$s</string>
    <string name="debug">Debug</string>
    <string name="release">Release</string>
    <string name="manufacturer">Manufacturer:</string>
    <string name="device_model">Device Model:</string>
    <string name="android_version">Android Version:</string>
    <string name="api_level">API Level:</string>
    <string name="snack_device_info_copied">Device info copied to clipboard</string>

    <string name="help_and_feedback">Help &amp; feedback</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="faq">FAQ</string>
    <string name="view_in_google_play_store">View in Google Play Store</string>
    <string name="version_info">Version info</string>
    <string name="version">Version %1$s</string>
    <string name="beta_program">Beta program</string>
    <string name="question_1">What is Android Studio Tutorials: Kotlin Edition?</string>
    <string name="summary_preference_faq_1">Android Studio Tutorials: Kotlin Edition is a free and open-source app that provides a collection of video tutorials on how to use Android Studio, the official integrated development environment (IDE) for Android app development.</string>
    <string name="question_2">How can I download Android Studio Tutorials: Kotlin Edition?</string>
    <string name="summary_preference_faq_2">Android Studio Tutorials: Kotlin Edition is available for download on the Google Play Store. Simply search for \"Android Studio Tutorials\" in the Play Store app on your Android device and tap \"Install\&quot; to download and install the app.</string>
    <string name="question_3">Is Android Studio Tutorials: Kotlin Edition available for iOS devices?</string>
    <string name="summary_preference_faq_3">No, Android Studio Tutorials: Kotlin Edition is currently only available for Android devices.</string>
    <string name="question_4">Is Android Studio Tutorials: Kotlin Edition suitable for beginners?</string>
    <string name="summary_preference_faq_4">Yes, Android Studio Tutorials: Kotlin Edition is suitable for beginners who are new to Android app development and want to learn how to use Android Studio. The app provides a range of video tutorials that cover the basics of using Android Studio, from installing the IDE to building and deploying your first app.</string>
    <string name="question_5">Is Android Studio Tutorials: Kotlin Edition updated regularly?</string>
    <string name="summary_preference_faq_5">Yes, Android Studio Tutorials: Kotlin Edition is updated regularly with new video tutorials and content to keep users up-to-date with the latest features and changes in Android Studio.</string>
    <string name="question_6">How can I get support if I have a question or problem with Android Studio Tutorials: Kotlin Edition?</string>
    <string name="summary_preference_faq_6">If you have a question or problem with Android Studio Tutorials: Kotlin Edition, you can contact us through the app\'s support page or by email at d4rk7355608@gmail.com. We\'ll do our best to help you resolve any issues you may be experiencing.</string>
    <string name="question_7">How do I disable Firebase analytics and crashlytics in Android Studio Tutorials: Kotlin Edition?</string>
    <string name="summary_preference_faq_7">You can disable Firebase analytics and crashlytics by going to the settings menu in the app and toggle the switch for these features.</string>
    <string name="question_8">How do I check for updates to Android Studio Tutorials: Kotlin Edition?</string>
    <string name="summary_preference_faq_8">You can check for updates to Android Studio Tutorials: Kotlin Edition by going to the settings menu in the app and selecting the \"Check for updates\" option.</string>
    <string name="question_9">How can I support the development of Android Studio Tutorials: Kotlin Edition?</string>
    <string name="summary_preference_faq_9">ou can support the development of Android Studio Tutorials: Kotlin Edition by leaving a positive review on the Google Play Store, sharing the app with friends and colleagues, and supporting the developers through the \"Share\" option in the settings menu.</string>
    <string name="feedback">Feedback</string>

    <string name="updates">Updates</string>

    <string name="support_us">Support Us</string>
    <string name="paid_support">Paid Support</string>
    <string name="summary_donations">No matter how much you donate, you will help us keep our app running and improve our features. We appreciate your generosity and kindness!</string>
    <string name="non_paid_support">Non-Paid Support</string>
    <string name="web_ad">Web Ad</string>

    <string name="snack_app_updated">The app has been successfully updated</string>
    <string name="snack_update_failed">The update process encountered an issue</string>
    <string name="try_again">Try again</string>
    <string name="summary_share_message">Check out this amazing app that I\'m using! It has some really cool features that you might find interesting. You can download it from the Play Store at: %1$s</string>
    <string name="learn_more">Learn more</string>

    <string name="close">Close?</string>
    <string name="summary_close">Are you sure you want to exit?</string>
</resources>